

Razibul Hasan

• Address: Hammacherstraße 46, 45127, Essen, Germany

Email address: razhasan93@gmail.com **\ Phone number:** (+49) 015739890108

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/razibul-hasan/

Date of birth: 18/12/1993 **Nationality:** Bangladeshi

ABOUT ME

AWS certified Solution Architect Associate with 3+ years of experience in related fields, Skilled in information management, application development, and other aspects of service-oriented architecture. Capable with an ability to identify and deal with a client's needs by translating them into appropriate technical solution/s.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[03/2018 - 11/2020] **IT Engineer**

Wallz

City: Dhaka

Country: Bangladesh

Main activities and responsibilities:

Working as a confident Information Manager for technical improvements and to enable business intelligence

[02/2021 - 12/2021] **Cloud Engineer**

Landknock

City: Dhaka

Country: Bangladesh

Main activities and responsibilities:

- Designed and edited blueprints for IT infrastructure and networking architecture according to management's demands.
- Monitored existing infrastructure and architectural frameworks for performance, and made changes and updates when necessary.
- Kept up to date with latest industry knowledge and news to maintain and improve enterprise and business platforms.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

[10/10/2021 - Current] M.Sc in Automation & Robotics

TU Dortmund https://www.tu-dortmund.de

Address: 44227, Dortmund, Germany Field(s) of study: Automation and Robotics

[2012 - 2017] **B.Sc in EEE**

Independent University www.iub.edu.bd

Address: Plot 16 Aftab Uddin Ahmed Rd, Bashundhara R/A, 1229, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Field(s) of study: Electrical and Electronic Enginnering

My Digital Skills

Cloud Engineering | AWS Solution Architect | Familiarized with Python | Serverless Computing | Docker | Linux | Github | Kubernetes | JENKINS

MANAGEMENT AND LEADERSHIP SKILLS

Team Player

- Analytical mind
- Collaboration
- Project management & delegation
- Risk identification & management
- Excellent communication skills

CERTIFICATIONS

[27/08/2022 - Current] AWS Solution Architect Associate

https://www.credly.com/badges/2bbbe76f-99a3-4685-9f74-1e401b2ce639/public_url